[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "Communicate with your neighbor..",
    "left": "through morse code",
    "right": "by shouting through the air vent"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Listen to your neighbor..",
    "left": "do the Macarena for 4 hours",
    "right": "learn the drums"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Greet your neighbor by..",
    "left": "taking off your imaginary top hat",
    "right": "with a high five and a wink"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Help your neighbor while he's on holiday by..",
    "left": "helping feed his pet snake",
    "right": "keeping his 100 year old bonsai tree alive"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Knock on your neighbors door and have them answer..",
    "left": "completely naked",
    "right": "in a clown costume"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Your building votes to..",
    "left": "have communal chickens",
    "right": "have a brewery in your basement"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Your garden be redone to feature..",
    "left": "a dormant volcano",
    "right": "a super massive black hole"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Your communal building party be..",
    "left": "a garden party in the middle of winter",
    "right": "an indoor Sankt Hans"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Throw your trash away..",
    "left": "once a month",
    "right": "carry out each piece of trash individually"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Your neighbor be..",
    "left": "a vengeful ghost",
    "right": "10 college party guys"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Every sunday morning hear..",
    "left": "roosters crowing",
    "right": "the couple next door arguing"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Your building basement was turned into..",
    "left": "a bingo club",
    "right": "a french film cinema"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Your upstairs neighbor does..",
    "left": "a 90’s aerobics workout at 6am every morning",
    "right": "a lot of diy work and they love their drill…"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The locks in your building..",
    "left": "be permanently broken",
    "right": "open with a 40 digit long alarm code"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Ask your neighbor for..",
    "left": "10 kilos of sugar",
    "right": "a glass of water"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "The board members of your building..",
    "left": "were 13 year old kids",
    "right": "make every decision with a coin toss"
  }
]
